[{"answer": "You know we're living in a society! my friend walks up from the ramp", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What's gonna happen? They can't kill us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'll be my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who's gonna be my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Who am I", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You could be Colin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We'll ask him.  My dear fellow, where are you dropping us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Of course, the uh, the four passes.  Four passes to Madison Square Garden? Wait a minute. Wait a minute! Of course! that place! that place are playing the that place tonight", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "We're going to the Knick game", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "First of all, you don't look like any my friend, period", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't want to be my friend anymor", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well you should have been my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, you have to be my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So we jump and roll, you won't get hurt", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We're slowing down. Are those the people", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Never", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There was no picture on the book jacket", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well then why would they take a limo from the airport", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "That's pretty strange. Did he say anything else", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Didja see the way she was looking at me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I know, I know. Kind of a cute Nazi though", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I can't run, I have a bad hamstring", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "--Astroturf? You know who's responsible for that, don't you?! The Jews! Ah, the Jews hate grass. They always have, they always will", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Limo.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Would you excuse us for a minute my friend, we're kind of in the middle of something", "qsentId": 28}]